neobits.com 2017-06-19

# Neobits.com is where business goes shopping. Offers the largest B2B catalog on the internet. Provides technology products, laboratory equipment, industrial and wireless infrastructure, software, audio-visual systems, materials and supplies from more than 10,000 manufacturers in 40,000+ categories. With over 5 million products and over $100 billion in inventory, we have what your business needs.

Our Internet store allows you to buy products and services, receive special discounts, apply for credit, fill out surveys, and receive newsletters, e-mails or other promotional information from us. We use the information that we collect about you to fulfill your product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience.

#### Personally Identifiable Information:

This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you order a product or service, enter contests or sweepstakes, apply for a lease, fill out surveys, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details.

We use customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems. We will disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties to charge your credit card, fill your order, deliver your order, provide customer service, provide you with credit and deliver promotional e-mails to you from neobits.com. We may also share your personally identifiable information with third parties who provide services to us, our customers and web site visitors. Those third parties include authorized contractors, temporary employees and consultants and other companies working with us (collectively, "agents"). Where we believe it to be appropriate (in our sole discretion), we will ask our agents not to disclose or use your personal information for purposes other than to provide services to you or neobits.com.

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent. We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of neobits.com, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency.

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Information:

This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We review the actions of the neobits.com visitors on an aggregate basis to determine customers' preferences.

#### Cookies:

We use cookies and may allow others to use cookies in the operation of our site.

#### Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement:

Occasionally neobits.com may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without prior notice to you. neobits.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful.

#### Sweepstakes and Drawings:

Where you enter a sweepstakes, drawing or other promotion, we may provide entry information, including name, address, email address and age to the company providing the prize or sponsoring the promotion. They may use your Personally Identifiable Information to send you marketing or promotional materials or other communications.

#### Updating your Personally Identifiable Information:

During the online ordering process you can review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted. You may change any of your personal information in your account online at any time. We encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result, you should not expect that all of your Personally Identifiable Information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases.

#### Security:

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. We do not store your credit card information after the completion of the transaction.

#### Children's privacy:

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 18 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at privacy@neobits.com so that we may delete the minor's information.

#### Third party sites:

Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. neobits.com is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

#### Contacting us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact neobits.com by sending a letter to:

  * Neobits, Inc.
  * Attn: Privacy
  * 3350 Scott Blvd., STE 4601
  * Santa Clara, CA 95054
  * USA

You may also contact us by e-mail at privacy@neobits.com.

#### Privacy Policy changes:

This Privacy Policy was last changed on November 16, 2003. If neobits.com makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.
